Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1991-2010; 7
  - 105th Congress, 1997-1998; 4
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Amendments, 1997-1998 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Education FY99, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Energy Assistance FY99, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Family Planning FY99, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Labor/HHS, FY98, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Health FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health, & Human Services and Education, Requests, Hispanic-Serving Institutions (HSI) FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Impact Aid FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, KERA FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Labor FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services and Education, Requests, Social Services FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Legislative Branch, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Legislative Branch FY98, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction FY99, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, Omnibus Appropriations, End of Session Wrap-up, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations, Oversight Plans, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Appropriations, Rule Changes, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Subcommittee, Allocations, FY98, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Subcommittee, Assignments, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Subcommittee, Selections (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Subcommittee, Selections (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Supplemental Security Income, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Texas A&M System Priorities FY98, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Title XX Social Services, Block Grant, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Transportation FY99, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Service, and General Government, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs and Housing and Urban Development, FY99, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Armed Forces, General, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Armed Forces, Army, Active Component/Army National Guard (AC/ARNG), 1998 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Armed Forces, Army Caucus, 1997-1998 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Armed Forces, Army, Family Medium Tactical Vehicles (FMTV) Program, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Armed Forces, Defense, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Armed Forces, Ft. Hood, Management of Endangered Species, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Armed Forces, Legislative Liaison Office, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Armed Forces, Military Construction, XXI Soldier Development Center, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Armed Forces, Navy, General, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Armed Forces, Navy, Nuclear Propulsion Program, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Armed Forces, Navy, Tactical Tomahawk Program, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Armed Forces, Texas Requests, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Armed Forces, V-22 Osprey Production, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Budget, General, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Budget, Babcock and Wilcox Plant in Paris, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Budget, Balanced Budget Act, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Budget, Clinton Budget FY 1999, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Budget, Congressional Budget Process, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Budget, Finance Reform, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Budget, Votes for Budget Savings, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Education, General, 1997-1998 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Education, Block Grants, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Education, Federal Education Spending (Q&A), 1997 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Education, High Hopes 21st Century Scholarship, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Education, Higher Education Amendments, HR 6, Additional & Dissenting Views, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Education, Higher Education Amendments, HR 6, Conference Report, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Education, Higher Education, HR 6, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Education, Impact Aid, General, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Education, Impact Aid, Coalition, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Education, Impact Aid, Construction Amendment, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Education, Impact Aid, DOD Money FY 98-FY 99, 1997-1998 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Education, Impact Aid, Federal Impaction Profile, TX, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Education, Impact Aid, Forward Funding, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Education, Impact Aid, FY 98-FY 99, 1997-1998 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Education, Principal/Superintendent Training, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Education, School Construction, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Education, State Student Incentive Grant, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Education, Student Loan Interest Rate, 1997-1998 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Education, TRIO Grants, TX, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Education, Voluntary and National Tests, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Energy and Water, Appropriations, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Energy and Water, Congressional Quarterly, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Energy and Water, Congressional Research Service Reports, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Energy and Water, Edwards’ Votes, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Energy and Water, Ft. Hood, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Energy and Water, Low Income Home Energy Assistance (LIHEAP), 1998 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Energy and Water, Notes and Memos, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Energy and Water, Requests, 1997-1998 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Energy and Water, Research and Development, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Energy and Water, Research Hearing, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Energy and Water, Restructure the Nation’s Electric Utility Industry, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Energy and Water, Superconductivity, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Energy and Water, Texas Compact Consent Act, General, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Energy and Water, Texas Compact Consent Act, Briefing Book (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Energy and Water, Texas Compact Consent Act, Briefing Book (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Energy and Water, Texas Compact Consent Act, Briefing Book--Updated (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Energy and Water, Texas Compact Consent Act, Briefing Book--Updated (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Energy and Water, Texas Compact Consent Act, Texas, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Energy and Water, TX Projects, 1997-1998 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Environment, Air Quality, 1997-1998 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Environment, Alcoa and Clean Air Regulations, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, General, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, Community Right to Know, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, EPA, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, Hearing, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, Limit Regulations, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, Research, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, Sierra Club, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Environment, Clean Air Standards, Support Regulations, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Environment, Mercury Lamp Recycle Projects, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Environment, Particulate/Ozone, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Environment, Propane, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Environment, Waste Water, Plumbing, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Affairs, General, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Affairs, China, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Affairs, Cooperative Fire Suppression Agreement With Mexico, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs, Expansion of NATO, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Committee on Standards of Official Conduct, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Constitution: Jefferson’s Manual and Rules of the House of Representatives, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Health, Blue Cross Blue Shield, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Health, Breast Cancer Coverage, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Health, Eye Health, 1997-1998 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Health, Family Planning, General, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Health, Family Planning, Title X, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Health, Health Maintenance Organizations (HMO’s), 1998 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Health, Homeless Youth Grant Program, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Health, Medicare, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Health, Medicare Part B Premium Penalty, 1998-1999 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Health, Meridian (TX) Hospital, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Health, Prospective Payment System, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Health, Tobacco, Free Kids Act, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Health, Tobacco, Texas, 1997-1998 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Interior, National Monument Fairness Act, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Interior, Point Reyes National Seashore Farmland Protection Act, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Judiciary, Bankruptcy Reform Act, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Judiciary, Citizens Access to Justice Act of 1998 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Judiciary, Naming the Department of Justice Building in Washington after Robert F. Kennedy, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Judiciary, Reducing the Availability of Pornographic Images to Children, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Oil and Gas, Royalty-in-Kind, Research, 1997-1998 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Postal Service, Auto Day, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Small Business Administration, Regional Administrator, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Social Services, Adoption, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Social Services, Housing, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Social Services, Manufactured Housing Improvement Act of 1998 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Tax, Democratic Tax Cut Alternative, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Tax, IRS, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Texas, Low-Level Radioactive Waste Disposal Compact, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Texas, National Weather Service, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Texas, Rail Congestion, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Texas, “The Turn: America at the Millennium”, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Texas, Voting Practices, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Texas, White House Office of Legislative Affairs, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Airports, TX, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, AMTRAK, WACO, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Building Efficient Surface Transportation and Equity Act, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Cooperative Air Services, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Waco Airport, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Veterans, General, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Veterans, Iraqi Claims Fund, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Veterans, Mental Health Illness Research Education and Clinical Center (MHIRECC), 1998 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Veterans, Regional Office, Doris Miller Name Designation, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Veterans, Persian Gulf Veterans, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Veterans, Texas Veterans Nursing Home, Temple, 1997-1998 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - 106th Congress, 1999-2000; 5
    During the 106th Congress, Edwards participated in debates on abortion laws and introduced a bill called the “Banning Late Term Abortions Act” that sought to make late term abortions illegal, except in cases where the mother’s health or life were at risk. For appropriations, materials on funding for the Department of Defense, Postal Services, and Military Construction are found. In education, Edwards signed a letter to the Secretary of Education supporting the Partnership for Texas Public Schools, which was seeking funding under the Teacher Quality Enhancement Grant program for teacher training and reforming Texas education; the Partnership’s application was approved and received funding. Numerous materials on legislation for Medicaid and prescription drugs are also in this subseries, as are materials regarding funding for airports in Texas and other requests from the Texas Department of Transportation.
    - Abortion, Abortion, 1999-2000 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Agriculture, Crop Insurance Reform, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Agriculture, Disaster Relief, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Agriculture, Disaster Relief, Department of Agriculture, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Agriculture, Food Safety/Product Liability, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, USDA, Civil Rights, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, General, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Agriculture, Rural Development, FDA & Related Agencies, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary, and Related Agencies, HR 2670, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Defense FY00 (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Defense FY00 (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Defense FY00 (Conference Report), 1999 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Defense FY01, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Energy, General FY 00, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Energy, Hearings FY 00, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Dept. of Energy, Requests FY 00, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Department of Interior & Related Agencies, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Department of Transportation, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Department of Transportation & Related Agencies, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, District of Columbia, Committee Print FY 00, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Energy and Water, Army Corps of Engineers FY 00, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Energy and Water, Development, HR 2605, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Energy and Water, Development, 2001, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Energy and Water, FY 00, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Energy and Water, FY 00, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Foreign Operations FY 00, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, General FY 01, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, Texas Requests FY 01, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Supplemental Appropriations FY 99, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, T/PO, Gun Control Amendments FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Amendments FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Bills and Committee Prints FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Family Planning FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Requests, Underage Drinking Prevention FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Sanders’ Amendments, Exchange Stabilization Fund FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Tiahrt Amendment, Commercial Mail Receiving Agencies FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Treasury, Postal Services, General Government, Walsh-Price Amendment, Federal Funded Research Subject to Freedom of Information Act FY 00, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Treasury-Postal Services, H.R. 2490, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, Interior & Related Agencies, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health, and Human Services, and Education, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Legislative Branch, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Milcon, Family Housing & BRAC, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Omnibus Appropriations Agreement, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Social Security/Medicare Lock-Box, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Armed Forces, Army Caucus, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Armed Forces, Children’s Education, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Armed Forces, Civil Air Patrol Appropriations, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Armed Forces, Department of Defense Instillations & ATM Surcharges, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Armed Forces, Ft. Hood Range Operations, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Armed Forces, Hillsboro & Marlin TX National Guard Armories Closure, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Banking, The Homeowners Insurance Availability Act, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Budget, Allocations Talking Points, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Budget, Economy, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Budget, FY 2001, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Suballocation of Budget Allocations, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Districts, Universities, National Institute for Environment, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Districts, Waco, Community Development Block Grant, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Districts, Waco, Lake Brazos, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Education, General, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Education, Congressional Staff Handbook, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Education, Early Head Start Funding, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Education, Education Savings Accounts, HR 7, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Education, Impact Aid, General, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Education, Impact Aid, Reauthorization HR 3616, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Education, Memos, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Education, Student Aid Program District 11, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Education, Student Loan Interest Rates, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Education, Teacher Empowerment Act, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Education, Teacher Quality Enhancement, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Education, Troops to Teachers, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Energy & Water, General (1of 2), 1999 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Energy & Water, General (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Energy & Water, Amarillo National Resource Center, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Energy & Water, Cowbird Trap Project, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Energy & Water, Fort Worth District, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Energy & Water, Gatesville, Grove Water Supply, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Energy & Water, Nuclear Power in Texas, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Energy & Water, Nuclear Waste Management, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Energy & Water, Radioactive Waste, Dumping, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Energy & Water, Radioactive Waste, FUSRAP FY00 (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Energy & Water, Radioactive Waste, FUSRAP FY00 (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Energy & Water, Security at Facilities, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Energy & Water, Subcommittee Requests & Hearings (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Energy & Water, Subcommittee Requests & Hearings (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Energy & Water, Water Resources Development Act of 1999 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Energy & Water, Wen Ho Lee Investigation, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Environment, General, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Environment, Blackland Research Center, 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Environment, Cement Kiln Dust, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Environment, Clean Air, Clean Air Act, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Environment, Clean Air, Damage Mitigation Solutions, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Environment, Clean Air, Emissions Standards, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Environment, Clean Air, EPA Suit, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Environment, Clean Air, Houston, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Environment, Clean Air, TX DOT, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Environment, Endangered Species Act, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Environment, EPA List of Hazardous Substances & Reportable Quatities, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Environment, Nuclear Waste, 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Environment, Propane, 1998-1999 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Environment, Rockwell Superfund Site, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Environment, Storm Water Regulations, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Environment, Superfund Liability, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Environment, Superfund Reform "Brownfield's Bill", 1999 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Environment, U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service Briefing Book, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Environment, Water Quality & Wastewater Disposal, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), Disaster Relief, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Constitution: Jefferson’s Manual and Rules of the House of Representatives, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, National Journal’s Congress Daily AM, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Gun Control Gun Control, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Health, Bipartisan Consensus Managed Care Improvement Act, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Health, Hospitals, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Health, Hospital Preservation and Equity Act of 2000 (HR 3580) (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Health, Medicare, 1999-2000 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Health, Medicare, Democratic/GOP Plans, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Health, Medicare, Give-Back, 199-2000 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Health, Patient Protection, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Health, Privacy, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Health, Rural Health Care, 1999-2000 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, General, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, Access, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, GOP Plan, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, Industry, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, Pricing (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, Pricing (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, Prescription Drug Parity Act, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Health, Rx Drugs, Seniors, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Health, Self-Referral Reform, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Health, Texas A&M College of Medicine/Scott & White Hospital, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Health, Texas Health Insurance Risk Pool, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Health, Texas Public Health Pilot Projects, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Immigration, General, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Immigration, U.S. Border Patrol Del Rio Sector, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Interior, Black-Tailed Prairie Dog, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Interior, Conservation and Reinvestment Act (CARA), 1999-2000 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Interior, Morris K. Udall Wilderness Protection Act, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Interior, National Park Service, Yellowstone, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Interior, Reagan on Mt. Rushmore, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Oil and Gas, Royalty-in-Kind (RIK), General, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Oil and Gas, Royalty-in-Kind (RIK), Department of Energy, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Oil and Gas, Royalty-in-Kind, Research, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 8)